♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
So, Cleveland,
you got to be pretty psyched
about President Ubama, huh?
W-What?
Well, I mean, you remember how
a lot of people said, like,
"Oh, Ubama's not gonna
be able to do it,"
but he's-he's
hanging in there.
Peter, it's "Obama."
Eh, You-bama, Me-bama,
We-bama, who cares?
It's a black guy in a suit,
let's just marvel at that.
Gosh, Cleveland,
it sure is great
having you back at The Clam,
even if it's just for a week.
(ringtone):
♪ My name is Cleveland Brown ♪
♪ And I am proud to be... ♪
Oh, hang on, that's
my cell phone.
Aw, Peter,
you're using the song!
Thank you.
Well, the numbers
ain't so good,
so we got to do everything
we can-- Hello, Lois.
Peter, where the hell are you?
You told me you were gonna clean
out those boxes in the basement
and put them in the attic.
Lois, it just sounds like
busy work.
It is busy work.
I'm trying to keep you
off the streets and off drugs.
I'm selling those candy bars!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you
want to buy some candy bars
so we can get some new uniforms
for our baseball team?
Where'd you get
those candy bars?
Peter, I need you home.
You also promised you'd fix
that shelf in the garage.
Oh, Lois, I'm losing you.
(makes static noises)
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Oh, hey, Lois.
This is somebody else now.
There must've been
a cross connection.
My name is Mike,
and I'm somewhere else
trying to make my own call.
Fine, Mike.
You tell Peter he's in trouble
when he gets home.
You can tell him yourself,
because Mike is Peter!
Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
That was very good, Peter.
I know!
(sighs)
Geez.
That's all my life is lately,
just a bunch of chores.
I'm sick of Lois always
making me do stupid stuff.
I know what you're saying,
Peter.
Bonnie's always making me do
all these impossible
household tasks.
BONNIE:
Joe, make sure you get
all the tire tracks
out of the carpet.
Learn to live with it, Bonnie!
There are tracks!
People make tracks!
Boy, I hear you, too.
It's a lot of work
just to keep
my single guy fridge
sufficiently depressing.
Let's see.
Ex-girlfriend's Yoplait.
Root beer from two Julys ago.
Here we go, expired milk.
(chuckles)
Oh, my God, Jenny,
look how young you look.
I sympathize with y'all.
Donna makes me listen to Gayle
King on XM Radio 19 hours a day.
I tried to kill myself by
swallowing a nail clipper,
but I passed it.
What the hell
happened to us?
We used to be able to do
whatever the hell we wanted.
Now here we are,
in the prime of our lives,
and we're slaves to our women.
I know. An exciting
day for me
is when I watch
wheelchair porn.
Boy, do the sparks
fly on those.
Oh, is it hot?
Nah, it's mostly just chairs
smashing into each other.
Sometimes the director
has to come on camera
just to turn the
chairs around.
Well, why don't we make
our own excitement?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know, like,
maybe the four
of us should
do something
to reclaim our freedom.
Like go on a road trip,
find some adventure.
Quagmire,
that's a great idea!
Let's do a road trip!
Who's in?
No. No, no.
No, n-not you, Seamus.
SEAMUS:
Ah, poo.
All right, listen up, ladies.
We got something to say and we
ain't taking "no" for an answer.
We are going on a road trip.
We don't know how long
we'll be gone,
and don't expect a call
from us to check in.
This trip is about men
being men.
We will drive
after a couple of beers
and not make a big
federal case about it.
We're gonna sneeze and not
put our hand over (bleep).
And there ain't nothing
you can do to stop us!
Yeah, okay with me.
- Sure.
- Fine.
That'll be nice.
It'll give us a chance
to have some girl time.
Oh. All right, then.
Where are you boys going?
We're going to New Orleans.
The party capital of America.
Home of the
All-You-Can-Pee Street.
I'll tell you one thing, it's
all about the beads down there.
We all know
what's going on here.
It's just implied,
but we all know
what's going on
in this thought bubble.
The kids don't know, but we do.
Boy, I'm sure getting my money's
worth out of this rental car.
Okay, all right,
I got one.
Would you rather be a hobo
with a five percent chance
of getting inherited
by a rich guy
or be Hitler two years before
the end of World War II?
'Cause you know you're gonna
have to shoot yourself,
but you still got two
more years as Hitler.
If you're the hobo, do you, uh,
have a place to sleep,
like an underpass or...?
Different every night.
As Hitler, can I change
certain policies
so that maybe I'm looked on
more favorably
at the end of the war?
No, you already screwed up
big-time-- lot of dead Jews.
Am I a blue state
or a red state hobo?
Blue, but
Midwestern blue.
Oh, boy.
(grumbling)
I don't think so,
it's cold out there.
Am I allowed
to alter the mustache?
Dude, why do you keep
trying to make Hitler work?
Am I allowed to kill other hobos
to increase my odds?
Kill anyone you
like; you're a hobo.
Am I a walking hobo?
No. Quagmire and Cleveland
are, but you're not.
So, wait, I would also
be a paralyzed Hitler?
Yeah.
Would I be
a black Hitler?
Yes. No.
Well, wait a minute,
now how come I got to be
crippled Hitler
and he's still white Hitler?
If you got such a problem with
it, Joe, just be the hobo!
This one isn't very fun.
Wait a minute, where are we?
Yeah, this doesn't look like
the main highway anymore.
You think we made
a wrong turn?
I hope not.
These backwoods parts
of the Deep South
ain't a place
you want to get lost in.
(siren wailing)
Oh, no.
Don't worry
about it, guys.
I read nowhere that Southern
sheriffs really want
to be talked down to by
big-shot Northerners.
Afternoon.
Officer, what is it?
We are in a tremendous
urban rush.
You fellas ain't from
around here, are you?
Hey, Sheriff,
I'm trying to learn Southern.
Is this saying anything?
A-doy-doy-doy-doy!
We're very sorry, Sheriff,
and we want to cooperate
to the fullest extent possible.
You threatening me?
Uh, no, sir.
Who you calling "sir," boy?
I'm an officer of the law,
paid by this county.
And I can't help noticing
you got a headlight out.
Really?
I don't see any...
And I see that turn signal
ain't working neither.
Now, look, sir,
I'm a police officer, too.
I know all the games;
I use them myself.
So what do you say
we just work something out?
So, you're a cop, huh?
Let me see your badge.
Looks like you're
a civilian now.
I'm gonna have to
search your vehicle.
Well, lookie here.
What do we got in this thing?
Oh, come on!
You planted that there!
We had drugs?
Oh, my God,
why am I driving drunk
when I could've been
driving high?
You boys are in
a lot of trouble.
Dispatch,
Sheriff Nichols.
Bringing in four
perpetrators
under suspicion of
drug possession.
Descriptions: one
African-American,
one crippled, one
skinny, one handsome.
Yes.
You're all coming down
to the station with me.
Aw, crap!
Hang on, hang on,
you guys.
Don't worry. I know how to
speak this guy's language.
Keith Urban.
Go on.
Brett Favre.
Uh-huh.
I'm listening.
William H. Macy?
You guys are going
away for a long time.
Look at this, Cleveland.
Front of the bus,
back of the bus,
middle of the bus--
you guys are doing great.
I can't believe this.
Two weeks in prison
on trumped-up charges.
That trial was a total sham.
Yeah, I knew we were in trouble
the minute I saw the jury.
Well, at least they're
a jury of our peers.
I don't think they see it
that way, Peter.
Hello, gentlemen.
I am the warden.
You are here
because you are criminals.
This is not a resort.
You will be worked harder
than you have ever
been worked in your miserable,
pathetic lives.
And play
harder, right?
I bet.
Step forward, maggot!
(grunts)
Next time, that'll be you.
Well, why wasn't
it him this time?!
Oh, I'm so scared.
(grunting)
Peter, stop it!
Yeah, you're real big when
you got that stick, ain't you?
Okay, I'll stop now.
This is so much fun,
isn't it?
I know.
What should we talk
about next?
I know, let's talk
about actresses.
Ooh, yeah.
I feel like Natalie Portman
thinks she's so much better
than everybody.
She's nothing, and her
husband's a nobody.
Why does Laura
Linney always
look like she's just
finished skiing?
I don't know
who that is.
Really? The Big C?
Love Actually?
No, never heard of her.
Would you know
who she was
if I said Tyler
Perry's Laura Linney?
Ooh, I love her.
Oh, God, it's so hot out here.
Yeah, you knew it was
gonna be hot when you heard
that lonesome slide guitar
and that hawk's cry.
(guitar plays somber riff)
(hawk screeches)
Hey! This ain't break time!
Get back to work!
♪ Gonna see Miss Liza ♪
♪ Gonna go to Mississippi ♪
♪ Gonna go to Mississippi. ♪
Man, listen to
what the black guys are doing.
We need a white
guy work song.
(lively music playing)
♪ Hello ♪
♪ How are you? ♪
♪ How's the folks? ♪
♪ What's new? ♪
♪ I'm great ♪
♪ That's good ♪
♪ Ha-ha ♪
♪ Knock wood ♪
♪ Well, well ♪
♪ That's life ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ How's the wife? ♪
♪ Got to run ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ Ta-ta ♪
♪ Olive oil ♪
♪ Good-bye. ♪
(shoes tapping rhythmically)
You Peter Griffin?
Oh, yeah, thanks.
What the hell is that?
It's a jet pack.
I'll come back for you guys,
I promise.
You're my friend and everything
and I feel bad saying this,
but I wanted to see you fail.
Official prediction:
when they let us out of here,
we're gonna have to go through
the prison gift shop.
(men grumbling)
Oh, I hate doing that.
That's how
they get you.
Man, it's gonna feel so good
to walk out of here tomorrow.
Yeah, you know,
the time actually went by faster
than I would have thought.
Uh, you know something?
We left Quahog to find adventure
and get away from all
those lame chores at home,
but I'll tell you this.
Looking back on it now, I don't
think our lives are so bad.
Yeah, I sure do miss Lois
and the kids.
I'll tell you one thing.
When I get home,
I'm gonna sleep like a log.
Hey, I'm gonna plug in the
night-light if you don't mind.
Actually, you know what?
I'm gonna go ahead and
ask you to not do that.
Knock off that chitchat!
It's lights out!
Oh, hey, Warden, since
it's our last night in here,
can I have a glass of milk?
I feel like having
dream diarrhea.
Last night?
Where do you think
y'all are going?
Says here you got another
30 days on your sentence.
What?! But the court said we're
supposed to go home tomorrow!
Well, the court
ain't here, is it?
(Warden laughs)
Oh, man, how the hell
are we gonna do this
for another 30 days?
(man chuckles)
That's the way
it goes around here.
Once you come in,
you're never allowed to leave.
I got my sentence extended
30 days once.
That was 45 years ago.
Oh, my God,
you hear that?
We're gonna be stuck
in here forever!
Oh, God, what are we gonna do?
Well, I know
what I'm gonna do.
If we're gonna be here a while,
I'm gonna find the biggest guy
here and kick his ass.
Wait a minute.
That's me!
Oh, no, I have a knife!
Oh, what are we gonna do?!
They're gonna keep us
locked up here forever!
We're not staying
in here forever.
- We're getting out of here.
- How?
We're breaking out.
What?
Look, sometimes in life,
you got to say, "What the hell,"
and just go for it.
I mean, that's how
we won the Revolutionary War.
Colonel, the British are too
entrenched across the river.
I've told the men
we'll hold our position.
Negative. Tell the men,
we're going across.
But Colonel Goatbanger,
we've...
No, we need to do this,
'cause... for...
'cause of... for strategy.
All right, if we're
gonna break out of here,
we got to get past
these guards.
Well, I got an idea.
It won't be pretty,
but bear with me.
(groaning)
Oh, no, I fell out
of my wheelchair!
(groaning)
(strained groaning, sighs)
Don't help me!
I need to do this on my own!
What are you doing, Joe?
You're embarrassing us.
Oh, really?
Are they looking?
No. They're actually going
to great lengths to avoid it.
Exactly. No one wants
to watch a handicap
struggle for independence.
This will buy us at least
15 minutes of averted gazes.
All right,
I'm gonna nail this home.
Oh! Oh, this is
so humiliating.
I'm about to be an
adult man crying.
(Joe sobs loudly)
I can't walk!
Why the hell
can't I walk?!
This isn't
part of the act anymore!
No, no, no, no,
don't look.
If you make eye contact,
you'll have to help.
Hey, they're
getting away!
Release the dogs!
(barking)
(high-pitched barking)
(barking continues,
chains jangling)
(barking)
Oh, we did it!
Your plan worked, Joe!
I told you those guards
would turn away.
Yeah, Joe, that
was amazing!
That was easier than taking
candy from a premature baby.
(rhythmic beeping)
I'm, uh...
I'm just gonna take this.
(loud laughter)
Hey, I got an idea
for something that's gonna
be so (bleep) funny.
(whispering)
Okay, Bonnie,
go get it.
It's in the closet.
Brian! Brian,
come out here!
What are you doing?!
I'm reading.
What... what... what...
What are you reading?
Well, I was just finishing
Jonathan Franzen's book.
You know, I'll admit
it has its moments,
but it's completely
overrated.
I mean, I'm not saying I
wrote something similar to it
several years ago,
but I am saying...
Grab him!
(laughter)
What? What? What? What?
Hey, what are you doing?! Hey!
- Get his paw! Hold still!
- Hey! Hey! Hey! What?
- Push him down onto all fours!
- No. What are you do...?
- I don't want to do this.
- If he really starts freaking out,
put your pinkie in his butt!
- Aah!
(laughter,
Brian groaning)
Calm down!
(grunting)
(laughter)
Now Stewie!
All right, I guess
this is the night bitches die.
I wonder what the
chain gang did today.
I hope we're not
missing anything cool.
Maybe we should go back.
Hey, guys, look,
there's a house.
Maybe there's something inside
we can use
to get these chains off.
It looks like
nobody's home.
Hey, these look like
handcuff and shackle keys.
How do you know that?
(chuckles)
These are handcuff
and shackle keys.
Hey, it worked!
You know, there's an awful lot
of pictures
of the sheriff in this house.
Well, he's a good-looking man.
I'll bet a lot of people
in town have pictures of him.
Oh, no! It's the sheriff!
Quick, into the closet!
(farting)
Who's there?
PETER (in high-pitched voice):
Just me, sweetie.
Oh, I didn't know
you were home.
What are you doing
in the closet there?
Um... wife things?
Oh, all right. Well, I'll only
be home for a minute.
Some prisoners escaped
from the work camp,
and I'm helping the warden
track 'em down.
Oh. Well, maybe you
should let 'em go.
You know I can't do that.
You're always working.
I wish you'd spend
more time at home.
More time with me.
Maybe you're right, honey.
Maybe I do work too much.
You know what?
I'm gonna let
those fugitives go.
You'd do that for me?
I'd do anything for you.
I love you.
I love you, too!
Now, come out here
and give me a kiss!
Peter, no!
Wait minute!
I don't have a wife!
(gunshots)
(gunfire continues)
(sirens wailing)
(tires squealing)
(train whistle blowing)
Head for the tracks!
(gunfire)
Oh, no!
They're shooting at us!
Good thing bad guys are
such terrible shots.
Man, these guys are elusive!
Quick!
Hop on!
- All right, we did it.
- We made it.
That was a
close one!
(sighs)
Well, guys, we made it.
Boy, I feel like
I haven't eaten in a week.
Hey, if we pass
a McDaniel's
or a Burger Queen,
let's hop out.
Oh, that's right,
we're on television.
Oh, I'd love a
flame-broiled Bopper!
So frustrating. We all know
what we're talking about.
(train chugging,
train whistle blowing quietly)
Well, this was
quite an adventure.
Yeah, it's good to be
back in familiar territory.
(gun chambers cocking)
Where do y'all think
you're going?
You boys are fugitives
of my county,
and I'm gonna take you back.
Oh, no!
I don't think so.
You're in my jurisdiction now,
Sheriff Butt Breath.
Wow, Joe,
how'd you pull that off?
I put in a call from
the McDaniel's pay phone
while you guys were getting that
nine-piece chicken McFingers
and those Diet Conks
and those Fresh Fries.
Oh, come on. They-They
don't own "French fries!"
You know, you got some nerve
driving around my town
with a busted headlight.
And a busted windshield.
And an untreated flesh wound.
(groaning)
You took an oath just
the same as me, Sheriff.
To protect and serve.
Not to harass and douche.
Just 'cause you have
a badge doesn't mean
you can treat people
any way you like.
And as a law enforcement
professional,
you have an obligation to be
more ethically upstanding
than the average man, not less.
Now, get the hell
out of my town.
Nice going, Joe!
Well, it's great
being back in the North
where people
are civilized.
Hey, what, are you guys
all on a date?
Gay!
Oh, my God, Peter,
what an experience.
But the important thing is
you're home safe.
Yeah. And you know, I guess I
learned something from all this.
(sighs)
You know what?
We've done this a billion
times, so you know what?
I'm just gonna
do the cadences.
(speaking gibberish)
(speaking
gibberish)
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru